WHEN LIFE GIVES YOU TANGERINES
Hello. Hi.
Wow, you look beautiful.
Could you help me? Oh my.
Well done.
-Help me with this.
-Okay.
Here we go.
YALASHANG FILM CLUB
One, two, three.
I'll take one more.
Smile.
One, two, three!
What does it mean if I can't go?
Tonight… is our last night.
Our last night before you join the army!
Do I really have to…
What's wrong with you?
Hey, who knows what will happen?
They say you don't know
until you walk down the aisle.
Just wait and see.
I'll see you in a wedding dress.
Ta-da!
It's so beautiful.
I should cover this up.
I kept my promise.
Oh? Hey, over here.
Hey!
Not knowing who might come back
or come anew,
my heart pounded…
Oh my!
I didn't pop it on purpose.
…and my feet felt like they were floating.
SUCH AN UNEVEN LOVE
A new person has also
come into my mom's world.
A squishy thing that claims to be human.
HAPPY FIRST BIRTHDAY
FROM YEOM BYEONG-CHEOL, NA MIN-OK
Evoking unexpectedly deep affection
despite being two generations apart,
an endearing monster has come the world.
Don't babysit your grandkid,
no matter how adorable.
They're even more adorable
when you only see them occasionally.
Once Geum-myeong gets married,
throw off the burden of parenting.
Live carefree and soar free.
Everyone says the kid has my eyes,
but the trap is from his mother's--
The jaw area.
What about your family?
Aren't they coming?
Well, you know…
I wouldn't take an unemployed son-in-law.
Well, what about your brothers?
They just said
they better not see our asses again.
-Faces.
-Sorry?
Faces.
-Feces?
-Faces!
Faces.
That's 19 grams.
Goodness, they mentioned "19 grams"
on the phone a dozen times.
They told me to go to college with it.
Goodness, that stingy old man.
Hasn't he heard of inflation?
He should pay the market rate for college.
They have money, don't they?
He got this for us by selling rice cakes?
Yes.
This grandpa drives a Mercedes, right?
Of course he does.
Everyone eats rice cakes.
Not a cool job though.
"Cool"?
Let's go.
YANG CHE-IL'S FIRST BIRTHDAY
Should you be spending on that now?
I'm going to do everything for him.
You always just got by on my birthday.
-At the time, it was all we--
-I'm sure.
It was only tough on mine.
How will you support your family now?
Planning to live with us forever?
-I'm working on a business plan.
-Business?
With Cheol-yong?
I told you not to run a pawnshop.
Life is all about the lucky strike--
I should just strike you, damn it.
Others mature when they have a family.
Why are you chasing empty--
I don't need your help.
Am I expecting much from you?
Just get up early, for starters!
Go to the loading docks or something.
-And look for a job!
-Seriously.
You want me to live like you?
Is that what you want?
Father.
You have to open the faucet fully
to fill the bucket up.
You get nowhere in life
trying to mend every leaking hole.
You know it too.
Don't just count on Geum-myeong.
Watch what I can do too!
I won't be the dad who orders pork belly
for three when my family eats out.
I'll be the dad
who orders five or six servings.
Why are you like that to your father?
Your heart softens as you age.
Even Steelheart gets scars.
Then Geum-myeong's mom
can comfort Geum-myeong's father.
Good grief.
How do you keep getting more spiky?
Frankly, you should be thankful
I've grown this much.
Kids grow as much as you believe.
Geum-myeong grew so much
because you believed in her fully.
You only ever doubt me,
so I've only grown this much.
You're unbelievable!
Carry the baby already!
My arms are hurting.
Goodness.
Here, give me Che-il. You two go inside.
Hurry, hand him over to me.
My sweet baby. Come here.
My goodness.
I really had no idea
my daughter would do this.
I felt betrayed.
I felt like my entire world fell apart.
I can't tell you
how sorry I am, and…
Goodness, if you get married pregnant,
you can't even get a brass ring,
let alone a gold one.
I never even got to have a wedding.
She won't ever get to wear a veil either.
Eun-myeong may still be struggling
to find his way,
but as a person--
I have nothing against Eun-myeong.
Why is that?
They say sons take after their fathers.
I've always envied your life
more than anyone else's.
You're the wife of a rich family.
On the kids' sports days,
I dragged three kids along on my own
under the scorching sun.
Then I saw your husband
fanning your back so you could cool off.
You've always had a knack
for noticing things.
It made me cry.
I wondered how you were so blessed
to be treated so well
and what sins I had committed
to step on such a pile of poop.
So,
is Hyeon-suk doing okay?
She doesn't know how to do anything.
Scold her if she doesn't know anything.
Scold her until she cries her eyes out.
I won't scold her.
I won't make her cry her eyes out.
I won't be giving Hyeon-suk a brass ring.
Okay?
If you want to see
your first grandson or Hyeon-suk,
feel free to visit them whenever you want.
Or call me to come out.
We share our children,
so we're in this together, right?
Goodness, how can he look
exactly like my daughter?
Dear me.
It seems like you can't win
against your daughter either.
The title of a poem my mom once wrote…
was "My Damn Child."
What's the big deal?
For crying out loud!
You little punk!
Is she off to save the country
or her company?
Good grief. Just give it to me.
Why buy Chivas
for a child's first birthday?
Cheol-yong must be out of his mind.
Because you and Dad look down on me,
she treats her only nephew's
first birthday like this, huh?
Your sister's having a rough time too.
Her company is also in deep trouble.
She acts all high and mighty
because she works at a big company.
But who takes care of you and Father?
Who'll care for you when you're sick?
As if you could take care of anyone!
Take care of yourself first. Yourself.
Don't be so harsh.
Even a crooked tree shades the weary.
The shock is even greater
as the rumors turn out to be true.
This is likely to have
a deep, significant impact on our economy.
Kwon Jae-hong reports.
This afternoon, Korea First Bank,
Kia's main banking partner,
announced at a press conference
that 18 of Kia Group's 28 subsidiaries…
It was a season of reaping what was sown,
whether it was a gold toad…
or a postdated check.
-Stop layoffs right now!
-Stop layoffs!
-We won't just leave like this!
-We won't!
-Stop layoffs right now!
-Stop layoffs!
-We won't just leave like this!
-We won't!
The Asian financial crisis
is dismantling corporations,
triggering widespread unemployment.
OVERSEAS BUSINESS DIVISION
ASSISTANT MANAGER
A particularly unforgettable winter
was on its way.
Dainong Group, the 34th largest company,
has effectively been dissolved
except for the Midopa Company.
Of the four subsidiaries subject
to protection, only Midopa was revived.
While Dainong Ltd. went into receivership,
Dainong Heavy Industries
and Metro Product…
Anyone can get approved!
100% credit card approval!
Ssangbangwool Development and Corporation,
which filed for composition yesterday,
were declared bankrupt.
Taeil, after financial struggles,
was designated today
for bankruptcy protection.
The debts of Taeil and its subsidiaries
totaled 970 billion won.
Chohung Bank and other bond creditors
will meet on the 24th…
Stocks have plunged again,
with KOSPI falling…
First of all, thank you
for giving me the opportunity
to be here in difficult times…
First,
thank you for the opportunity
to interview during this difficult time.
I am willing to do…
After barely holding on
through severe financial struggles,
Haitai Group finally filed
for bankruptcy today.
This toothpaste was exported
across Northeast Asia
and was often unavailable
due to high demand,
but due to the manufacturer's bankruptcy…
This toothpaste alone fights
common cavities
and gum disease
and whitens stained teeth.
This product is the result
of a technical collaboration
with an American toothpaste company
recognized by the WHO. And so…
Newcore Group, the 25th largest company,
filed for composition
and was declared bankrupt today.
Dear viewers,
the government has decided
to request a bailout from the IMF.
Despite its reputation
for economic success,
Korea has been forced
to admit national bankruptcy
and seek recovery with assistance
from international organizations.
The government aims
to minimize the IMF policy intervention,
even if Korea receives its bailout funds.
The next stop is Sillim Market,
formerly known as Cannes Theater.
CANNES THEATER WILL SHUT DOWN
ON DECEMBER 1
When one door closes…
another is bound to creak open.
TICKET, JA 17
Hey, can't you just sit anywhere?
JA 17
This isn't a leg rest. It's an armrest.
It's an armrest.
You need countless lifetimes of fate
to meet even once in this life,
so the third time should be the charm.
Hey, did you see her?
Did you meet her?
-Sorry?
-You didn't see her?
Who told you to clean up?
I lined her up for you,
and you still missed the goal.
If even the third time fails…
you must wait for the next life.
Geum-myeong!
Last time, it was Seo Taiji.
This time, it was H.O.T.
Geum-myeong!
Only then did he realize.
You only get three chances.
If no one scores in extra time,
it will go to a penalty shootout.
Stop!
Sir!
When one door closes,
another is bound to creak open.
Could've caught the next one.
Goodness.
Thank you.
If the IMF crisis hadn't happened…
If I hadn't lost my job…
If the theater hadn't gone
out of business…
If any of those gears had failed
to do their part…
Everyone off. This is the last stop.
…perhaps this moment
would never have happened.
Is this a dream?
Is it?
Yes.
I chased you from the theater.
I ran like mad.
I couldn't let you slip away,
even if it meant losing my breath.
Were you
alone at the theater?
-Yes.
-I see.
-Were you also--
-Yes.
Finally.
This is when we use
the word "finally," right?
Why do you keep laughing?
You look totally different now.
I guess you're not Picasso anymore.
I am.
I'm the Picasso
at a place called Picasso Art Academy.
Our academy would be ruined without me.
They pay me well.
It's just so great.
Really.
Me too.
It's just so great.
How did we both end up
at the theater today?
I actually went every day.
Just in case.
I really missed you.
I missed you a lot.
So we can now…
"Now"?
Or shouldn't we?
A lager, please.
Still, we shouldn't?
Oh, we can order alcohol now.
Let's order beer.
Just beer?
JINRO SOJU
Wait.
Why do you keep staring?
It's driving me crazy.
I know, right?
It's also
driving me crazy.
-Oh my.
-Oh no.
I usually don't get drunk easily.
You'll hurt yourself.
Just lift your foot a little. Yes.
You sound just like my dad.
What was that sound you just made?
Are you bleeding?
I think it's a cut.
I think we need to apply pressure.
It's not bleeding though.
Preemptive steps.
How can this be?
I feel like I'm about to drop dead…
"Drop dead"?
When I used to carry those books for you,
I kept thinking,
"I want to hold her hand."
But we were…
See?
This is why I said,
"Everyone has a dark side, after all."
…no longer innocent.
I think I've gone to the darker side.
We dated like grown-ups…
more like La-Z-Boy than IKEA.
Are you out of your mind?
What's with your face? And your hands?
Come on. Stop making that face.
Come on. Are you drawing me
like they did in Titanic?
Come on. How can I draw you
The model is different,
and so is the situation.
"The situation"?
Well, what should the situation be?
Wow.
-Come on, Park Toto.
-"Park Toto"?
Then what should the situation be?
Toto keeps going to the dark side, huh?
God, seriously.
Come on. How could you spit on my face?
Stop calling me Park Toto!
Why do you like Park Toto so much?
I thought you never laughed at anything.
Toto and I shared the same sense of humor.
You're rubbing off on me.
I'm starting to talk like you too.
In a grown-up world
where we learned to fake smiles,
it was an incredible booster.
Don't make me laugh while we're kissing.
I can't focus.
Babe, it's harder
to laugh together every day
than it is to kiss every day.
That's why we're a good match.
-Don't add garlic for now.
-Okay.
Do you really like raw fish?
You always eat it.
Yeah, I do.
Hey, do you want to eat
some real amberjack?
-Real amberjack?
-Yeah.
Real amberjack.
And finally…
Finally, the two men met.
Darn it.
Amberjack, my foot.
Where did this damn saury come from?
Hey, Dad.
Why are you looking at him like that?
You'll make my man uncomfortable.
The day came when I sided
with my man over my old man.
This is how I look at people.
Try to look at him with some kindness.
Being on a boat isn't easy
for someone from the land.
Was it easy for you from the get-go?
-Yeah.
-Yeah, right.
Are you letting them go
because they're still too small?
You're such a kind fisherman.
Your father
is so kind.
They're bait.
We're throwing them to their deaths.
Not so kind now, huh?
Come on, stop glaring at him
and catch me an amberjack.
I brought him here
to eat some real amberjack.
Why do you keep following her?
Why? She's just going to the toilet.
Just sit and eat some amberjack.
And pay for what you eat.
AUNTIES' SEAFOOD HOUSE
Rice cakes for sale!
IMF CRISIS, HALF PRICE FOR JEJU CITIZENS
LET'S EAT AND SURVIVE TOGETHER
Rice cakes for sale!
Someone, buy her rice cakes.
Why won't anyone buy her rice cakes?
Rice cakes for sale!
GATHER THE GOLD IN OUR CLOSETS
TO REVIVE THE NATION'S ECONOMY
Rice cakes for sale!
Are they playing a game
where the first one to speak loses?
GOLD COLLECTION CAMPAIGN PARTICIPANTS
But why aren't you sitting over there?
Why do you ignore them?
Maybe she doesn't like him.
You don't? What do you think of him?
Me?
Get your head off my shoulder!
So why are you here?
Why did you come to Jeju?
Are you playing 20 Questions or what?
I told you not to be like that.
You can't talk, ride boats,
or even drink, huh?
Why should I give my daughter to you?
Would you, if you were me?
I'm angry for absolutely no reason.
But even now, you're not even trying.
Even if I wanted to impress you,
if you don't like me…
no matter what I do--
He won't like you in any case,
so you won't even try to suck up?
Who do you think you are?
You little brat. You're so damn rude.
Let go.
Ten, nine, eight--
Seven, six, five, four,
three, two, one. What?
I said let go.
What do you think of him?
Well,
you know…
You have something to say?
If you do, just say it. Come on.
Here's the thing.
His family…
You know, his family…
I mean,
I'm doing whatever I can to impress you.
What did you do?
I haven't noticed a thing this whole time.
I normally don't eat much, but…
Sorry for preparing too much food.
Watch it.
I'm this close to actually beating you up.
Don't glare at me.
Why are you getting up again?
Why keep following her to the toilet?
What are you trying to do?
What are you going to do in the dark?
You'll be dead meat.
It's dark, so I have to--
Attention!
It's dark, so I'll…
It's cold, so…
Why the hell is that punk so stiff?
What if Yang likes him
more than he likes her?
No, what if my sister
is making a fuss over nothing--
Did you just call
your brother-in-law "punk"?
"Brother-in-law"? So you approve of him?
You selfish kid.
Don't eat all the shrimp by yourself.
Peel a few for him!
Wait, why? What is it about him?
Seriously, why?
My God.
Why do you keep following her?
Why? She's just going to the toilet.
Just sit and eat some amberjack.
And pay for what you eat.
Good grief, why do you keep…
In case she falls.
In case Geum-myeong falls.
You think I'd let my daughter fall
into the water?
You should worry about yourself.
Hey, attention.
Attention!
Still, I should protect her, so…
I'm worried, so…
I don't stand a chance.
How am I supposed to impress him?
You know what, babe?
You were a bit stiff in there.
Well,
I want to impress him,
but this is just how I am, and--
So that's just how you are.
I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
It's hard to do things I never do, so--
So you think I'm the kind of person
who normally sucks up to others
and changes my voice around your mother
just because that's who I am?
Let me be clear. I'm…
-Are you listening?
-Yes.
I am my dad's daughter.
If my dad says no, that's a no for me too.
-No wedding bells.
-Babe.
Babe.
Wait, why do you approve of him?
Then why didn't you approve of my wife
from the get-go?
I won't stand anyone
treating my Hyeon-suk differently.
Go away. Just go.
Hey, does your Hyeon-suk know
you pooped your pants in kindergarten?
Does your Chung-seop know
you used my razor?
-Let go of me.
-Father!
Oh my.
Father.
Father!
Is it okay for me
to peel some shrimp for you?
Peel them for yourself.
He gets weird when he's drunk.
Look at him.
He absolutely adores Geum-myeong.
But you know,
his mom really wants Geum-myeong too.
She says she's really fond of Geum-myeong.
Isn't it funny?
Yep, it's so funny. It sure is.
You cried, didn't you?
Why would I?
Who in the world
wouldn't love our Geum-myeong?
You cried.
This is really wild honey
from Hallasan, right?
You're going to give this to his mom,
aren't you?
Well, you know,
Chung-seop's mom gave me a gift first.
She practically bribed me.
Not everyone would do that.
You know what I got yesterday?
What is this, some kind of treasure?
What could it be
that she'd pack so tightly?
Why are we letting him sleep here?
We should just get him a room at an inn.
How can we tell him to sleep at an inn?
I feel bad enough
that he has to sleep in the living room.
How can I sleep
under the same roof as Park Chung-seop?
Why can't you sleep?
I just can't.
Seriously, stop going out to check him.
He's not going to sneak
into Geum-myeong's room.
How can he
when you're glaring at him like that?
Don't!
Let me go. Hey.
Just sit down! Goodness!
Father, why do you keep coming out here
instead of going to sleep?
What about you? Why aren't you sleeping?
Why not? What is it?
What are you going to do?
What? What's wrong? Is there a problem?
I went home in the fall,
picked the best persimmons.
I put in effort all season long,
thinking of giving them to you.
I made these, looking at them every day,
just like gazing at lovely Geum-myeong.
That's how fond I am of Geum-myeong.
FROM CHUNG-SEOP'S MOM
Perhaps Mom
had been waiting for a long time
to hear those words.
Gonna stand watch all night?
And just what will you do
if he goes into Geum-myeong's room?
He'll be dead meat.
What can you do?
Has Geum-myeong's dad
ever once won against her?
Let her go now.
Your uneven love.
Mom knew…
that this would happen eventually.
Single Bungle Show!
I'm your host, Kang Seok.
The IMF crisis brought about
many gloomy terms, didn't it?
"MUTT."
Most are Unemployed in Their Twenties.
STORE CLOSING SALE
"The 38th Parallel."
If you're 38, you must resign.
"RAFFLE."
Retire At Forty-Five Like Everyone Else."
"Job thief."
Working until 56 makes you a thief.
It truly is a world without smiles.
Well, let's listen to an uplifting song.
Just like that, I leapt from the nest.
Like a bluebird soaring
above a bare mountain,
fluttering with excitement
and brimming with confidence.
Don't smile too much today.
It'll annoy your father.
Mom, don't do that today.
Don't cry like this, okay?
Come on.
Are you done with me once I'm married?
You won't be my mom?
Listen to me.
I'll still be Yang Geum-myeong,
not Park Geum-myeong.
What are the last digits of my pager?
Not his home number, right?
It’s still our family's 3312, right?
Then which family would I belong to?
I know. I'm not giving my daughter away.
So don't cry.
If you cry, I'll cry.
All the wedding photos will be ruined.
Let's keep it nice and cool.
Okay?
Oh dear! How did you make it here?
How could I miss
your family's celebration?
The girl who's getting married…
Can you straighten this?
…is the one who loved caramel, isn't she?
Yes, it's Geum-myeong.
You always gave her free caramel.
Yes, go ahead, please.
Wow, you look pretty today.
-Hey, where's Ju-gyeong?
-Ju-gyeong?
-How can the photographer be late?
-There she is.
-Hey!
I shouldn't have come.
-Ju-gyeong!
-Hey!
-Hurry!
Come on, hurry.
Hey, hurry.
What was that?
She looks so damn beautiful.
Hey, the photographer can't be late.
You should've started snapping
when I got out of the car.
Are you happy? You're one confident bride.
-Come on.
-Start taking pictures of me from here.
Okay.
So pretty.
Let's go over there.
Go to the steps.
Those steps.
Does everyone marry
their most passionate love?
The size of the love wasn't different.
Its temperature was.
You sent us so many tangerines.
You never have to buy
another tangerine again.
It was the temperature
that let me be myself.
Did you say hello?
I've found my prince.
What a match made in heaven.
Did you teach him to be cringy,
or is it him?
He's my top student.
How lovely.
Next, the groom will enter.
The groom is making a confident entrance.
Please welcome him
with a round of applause.
Did I not say I hate it
when brides cry at their weddings?
Don't you dare cry, Dad.
If you cry, I'll really get annoyed.
Never mind. You know what?
Just try not to look me in the eye, okay?
Geum-myeong.
You can do well, right?
If things go wrong, back down.
Just run straight to me, okay?
Okay?
Can you really eat this?
If you don't like it, back down.
Just spit it out, okay?
Goodness.
YANG GEUM-MYEONG
Do these fit?
Say, "Hello, teacher."
Hello, teacher.
Goodness me.
I'm telling you,
we can't send her to school yet.
Let's just send her next year.
You want to keep her at home forever?
How will you ever marry her off?
You're being so silly. Isn't he silly?
Geum-myeong,
you think you can go to school?
I can. Jeong-geun went too.
What does it matter if he went?
I don't like you being close
with Jeong-geun.
I want to go to school.
Then go for now,
and if you don't like it, back down.
Just run straight home, okay?
I'll be at home.
-All right?
-Okay.
Geum-myeong,
you can run well tomorrow, right?
I think I might come in first.
First place?
-Ready… That's not it.
-Go!
Run at "Go," okay?
But you don't have to come first.
Back down if you want.
If you fall, just run straight to me.
I'll be right behind you tomorrow. Okay?
Okay.
-Ready--
-Go!
Oh dear.
YOU CAN EASILY SCORE HIGH!
COLLEGE ENTRANCE EXAM IDENTIFICATION SLIP
Come on!
You got this!
Let's go, Munil High School!
We're here way too early again.
Seriously.
Why is our family so diligent?
What kind of lives have you led
to be like this?
Geum-myeong.
-You can guess well, right?
-Come on.
Why would I guess the answers?
Dad, I'm Yang Geum-myeong.
You're right.
I know from years of seeing you
that you do everything well.
You're good at everything.
Dad knows that now.
So you'll just say I do everything well?
You won't tell me to back down?
Still, if your head hurts
and you just can't do it, just back down.
Just run straight out.
I'll be right here. Okay?
You're always my backup, huh?
Are you sure you don't need
any herbal calming remedies?
YANG GEUM-MYEONG
THE PRIDE OF DODONG!
MY DAUGHTER WILL GET IN!
Every time I walked the tightrope,
my dad stood there holding the net.
"I'll be there even if you fall."
I wish I had told him
how comforting his words were
at least once.
While he was standing there,
it seemed the snow fell only on my dad.
The bride will now enter
and walk down the aisle.
Geum-myeong.
What?
Dad's still right here.
Just do everything you want.
Whatever you want.
Amid my dad's winter,
I grew into lush green.
Feeding on their verdant youth,
I became a tree.
If Chung-seop annoys you, come back to me.
Dad's always here for you. Okay?
No. Don't say things like that right now.
You're so annoying, Dad.
Please welcome the bride.
Please give her a warm round of applause.
Gwang-rye must be beaming from ear to ear.
She must be so happy at last.
When Ae-sun walked down the aisle
holding her uncle's hand,
I thought I'd just die from heartache.
The daughter's respectable life
felt like a medal to her mother,
so she kept smiling.
In case the bride didn't come
because she was crying,
the groom rushed out to greet her.
Please give them
another big round of applause.
We said we'd keep it cool.
Why are you bawling?
Aren't we getting married?
Should we call it off?
No, I'm going to do it.
Let's go.
It was only the day before my dad left me
that I rushed to pour out apologies,
"Dad, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry."
Dad told me back then
that he had been living in heaven
since the day I was born.
I told you
your father would cry more than your mom.
My dad's crying?
I didn't think
your dad would be like that.
Why do men want to act tough
around their sons-in-law?
Why drink more than he can handle?
Dad wants to see
if he gets weird when he's drunk.
Who's the weird one now?
-Hey, Dad.
-Come on!
What about your mom?
Sorry?
Does she like Geum-myeong or not?
My mother has always been harping on
about wanting a daughter,
so she likes Geum-myeong more than me.
No.
-I'm sorry?
-She's my daughter, not your family's.
She's my daughter forever.
Right. Of course.
-Park Chung-seop!
-Yes, Father.
Do you have any idea
what you're taking from me?
Sorry?
I am giving you…
my heaven.
To you, who did absolutely nothing for her
throughout her 30 years of life.
Well,
I heard that Mother was the literary one.
Hey, Yang Heaven.
Carry your own honey.
Dad had his uneven love stolen away
just like that.
We now ask the bride and groom
to face the bride's parents.
Bride and groom,
please bow to the bride's parents.
Oh dear, the bride's father is crying.
My goodness!
Be quiet.
The bride's father
must've truly loved his daughter.
Gwan-sik is being robbed
of his most precious treasure.
He's being robbed of it!
He wouldn't cry like that
even if his mother got remarried.
I wish you well. Go on.
Next, the bride and groom
will bow to the groom's mother.
Enough is enough, okay?
You're so embarrassing, seriously.
Bride and groom,
please bow to the groom's mother.
Who is it?
Who's looking for you?
Who is this?
I don't know either.
Didn't I tell you to dye your gray hair
before going?
Geum-myeong nagged me about it again.
Obviously, I'd take better care
of my own husband than she would, right?
She's got her husband to look after now.
Life never allows us
to truly savor these moments.
Yang Eun-myeong.
Me?
Happiness comes right at you.
Misfortune always creeps up from behind.
Where is Park Cheol-yong?
You know, right?
Me?
When Mom says
not to hang out with a certain friend,
there's always a good reason.
"IF YOU CAN'T, JUST BACK DOWN.
WE'RE ALWAYS HERE FOR YOU."
Subtitle translation by: Sung In Jang